http://www.girlscoutsaz.org/en/about-our-council/gsacpc-privacy-policy.html

My GS
ABOUT ACTIVITIES COOKIES +VOLUNTEER CAMPS GIVE OUR COUNCILAbout UsNewsContact UsForms & DocumentsBoard of DirectorsAlumShare Your StoryEmployment OpportunitiesOur MagazineAnnual MeetingESPAÑOLMy GS
Contact Us
Shop
Forms
About UsNewsContact UsForms & DocumentsBoard of DirectorsAlumShare Your StoryEmployment OpportunitiesOur MagazineAnnual Meeting
About Our CouncilGSACPC Privacy Policy
GSACPC Privacy Policy
This Web site is owned by Girl Scouts–Arizona Cactus-Pine Council,
Inc., a 501(c)(3) non-profit organization headquartered Phoenix, Arizona.
Girl Scouts–Arizona Cactus-Pine Council, Inc. is committed to
respecting and protecting the privacy of our visitors. This privacy
policy discloses how we collect, protect, and use information you
provide or we collect online, as well as how we protect children's
privacy. If our policy practices change in the future, we will let you
know by posting our revised privacy policy on our Web site. By using
the pages on this site or other services covered by the posted Privacy
Policy, you are accepting the practices described in the Privacy Policy.
INFORMATION COLLECTION
Personally Identifiable Information. At our site, we do not collect
personally identifiable information from individuals unless they
provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. This means we do not
require you to register or provide information to us in order to view
our site. Girl Scouts–Arizona Cactus-Pine Council, Inc. only gathers
personally identifiable data on our site, such as names, addresses,
Zip/postal codes, e-mail addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted
by a visitor.  Once collected, we may combine this information with
other information collected from external sources.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Girl Scouts–Arizona
Cactus-Pine Council, Inc. may automatically collect certain technical
information from your computer such as your Internet service provider,
your Internet Protocol address, your browser type, your operating
system, the pages viewed, the pages viewed immediately before and
after accessing the Web site, and the search terms entered to get to
our site. This information allows us to improve and customize our
services. We and our service providers may collect this information
using “cookies,” which are small text files that many websites save on
your computer, or similar technologies. See the section on “Use of
Cookies and Similar Technology” below for more information.
USE AND SHARING OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION
The personally identifiable information you provide is used by Girl
Scouts–Arizona Cactus-Pine Council, Inc. and other entities who are
involved in the operation of this site or who provide support for the
Girl Scouts–Arizona Cactus-Pine Council, Inc. and Girl Scouts of the
USA mission and programs, for general business purposes and for the
purposes for which you provided the information.  General business
purposes include, for example, Girl Scouts–Arizona Cactus-Pine
Council, Inc. and Girl Scouts of the USA membership activities,
program participation, marketing, promotions, and fundraising
activities and communications.  The purposes for which you provide
information includes our use of your personally identifiable
information to process online transactions, purchases, and donations,
facilitate participation in Girl Scouts of the USA and Girl
Scouts–Arizona Cactus-Pine Council, Inc. programs, promotions and
services, or process job applications.  We do not sell information you
provide to us online with third parties.  We may share personally
identifiable information with third parties including: (i) with other
Girl Scout Councils and Girl Scout troops for administrative purposes
relating to a child’s activities with another Council or their troop;
(ii) when the person submitting the information authorizes us to share
it; (iii) when sharing the information is with a service provider in
furtherance of our operations or the operation of the site, for
instance, to process a purchase or other transaction you make; (iv) to
facilitate participation in Girl Scouts of the USA and Girl
Scouts–Arizona Cactus-Pine Council, Inc. programs, promotions, and
services, or to engage in fund raising, marketing communications and
promotions; (v) to comply with legal processes such as a subpoena or
court order or to otherwise protect your or our legal rights; or (vi)
for other purposes for which you provided the information. Girl
Scouts–Arizona Cactus-Pine Council, Inc. has no control over or
responsibility for the data collection and use practices of third
parties that process online transactions.  For example, if you make a
purchase on our site using a PayPal account or similar account of a
third party payment provider, certain information is transmitted to
the payment provider and is subject to the third party’s own privacy policy.
Please note that Girl Scouts of the USA provides operational support
for the site and may collect and use personally identifiable
information you provide to the site and other information collected by
the site as described in this policy.  Girl Scouts of the USA will use
any information it collects for the purposes described in this policy
and in a manner consistent with its own privacy policy, which is
available here.  Girl
Scouts–Arizona Cactus-Pine Council, Inc. and Girl Scouts of the USA
are each responsible for their own information handling practices.
CHILDREN’S PRIVACY
Girl Scouts–Arizona Cactus-Pine Council, Inc. is committed to
providing a safe, secure, and fun online experience for children who
visit our site. We are dedicated to safeguarding any personally
identifiable information collected online and to helping parents and
children have positive experiences on the Internet.
We will never knowingly request personally identifiable information
from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental
consent. With parental consent, we may collect information from
children under the age of 13 such as: name, address, email address,
account information, and user generated content. This information
allows us to fulfill a requested transaction and facilitate
participation in online programs, keep records, undertake certain
marketing activities, or to otherwise customize or enhance the Web
site experience for children.
Children under the age of 13 may be able to make certain content
such as user generated content visible to others or the public. This
could include, for example, a webpage or parts of webpages operated by
children that have been designed for group or public viewing. However,
absent parental consent, children under 13 would be allowed to display
only limited information such as a first name or unique user name or
other information that does not allow for online contacting by third parties.
Regardless of what information is displayed, parents can revoke
their consent and ask that information about their children be deleted
from the site by contacting our offices by phone at 602-452-7000 or
1-800-352-6133 or via email at council@girlscoutsaz.org.
To do this or to review personally identifiable information collected
from children, we must verify the identity of the requesting parent.
When a parent revokes consent, we will stop collecting, using, or
disclosing information from that child. To respect the privacy of
parents, information collected and used for the sole purpose of
obtaining verifiable parental consent or providing notice is not
maintained in retrievable form by the site if parental consent is not
obtained after a reasonable time.
Submissions
Girl Scouts–Arizona Cactus-Pine Council, Inc. welcomes children to
learn more about our organization and, where appropriate, participate
in polls and surveys, as well as submit comments, artwork, writings,
and other submissions for posting on our Web site. For this reason,
Girl Scouts–Arizona Cactus-Pine Council, Inc. follows the guidelines
for interactive electronic media published by the Children's
Advertising Review Unit (CARU) of the Better Business Bureau for pages
targeted to children under 13. However, we encourage this be done only
with their parent's knowledge and supervision. We also encourage
children to use an alias (e.g., "Bookworm",
"Skater", etc.), first name, nickname, initials, or other
alternative to full names or screen names which correspond with an
e-mail address for any activities which will involve public posting.
In keeping with CARU's Principle regarding respecting and fostering
the parents' role in providing guidance for their children, we
encourage parents to check and monitor their children's use of e-mail
and other online activities regularly.
USE OF COOKIES AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES
Visitors should be aware that non-personal information and data may
be automatically collected by the Girl Scouts–Arizona Cactus-Pine
Council, Inc. Web site through the use of "cookies" or other
similar technologies such as web beacons. "Cookies" are
small text files a Web site can use to recognize repeat visitors,
facilitate the visitor's ongoing access to and use of the site, and
allow a site to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that
will allow content improvements. Cookies are not programs that come
onto a visitor's system and damage files. Generally, cookies work by
assigning a unique number to the visitor that has no meaning outside
the assigning site. If a visitor does not want information collected
through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most
browsers that allows the visitor to deny or accept the cookie feature.
“Web beacons” are a small snippet of code embedded in webpages
typically used to monitor activity on a webpage and transfer or
collect information, such as information about your Internet Protocol
address, the URL of the page on which the beacon is located, the
browser type that is accessing the site, and the ID number of cookies
placed on your computer.
Girl Scouts–Arizona Cactus-Pine Council, Inc. uses
"cookie" technology only to obtain non-personal information
from its online visitors in order to improve visitors' online
experience and facilitate their visit within our site. Girl
Scouts–Arizona Cactus-Pine Council, Inc. may use web beacons to
improve website services, conduct website analytics, first party
advertising relating to us and our sponsors, and to optimize the
browsing experience.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit
our Web site. These companies may use non-personally
identifiable information (that is, not including your name, address,
e-mail address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and
other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and
services of interest to you on this or other websites. Read more
information about this
practice at http://www.networkadvertising.org
and http://www.aboutads.info/choices/
to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies.
LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES AND SERVICES
This site may be linked to other sites and services that are not
maintained by Girl Scouts–Arizona Cactus-Pine Council, Inc. These Web
sites have their own privacy policies, which you should review prior
to visiting them. We have no responsibility for linked Web sites and
provide these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors.
OUR SECURITY SAFEGUARD
The safety and security of your online experience is of the utmost
concern to us. We take measures to implement reasonable physical,
electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent
unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the
information we collect online.
Credit Card Safety
Protecting the safety of your credit card information is also
important to us.  For card transactions we process, we use Secure
Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect the security of your credit
card information as it is transmitted to us. SSL is an Internet
encryption technology, and a method of scrambling data as it travels
from your computer to our Web site servers. We also encrypt your
credit card number when we store your order and whenever we transfer
that information to participating merchants.
To make sure you are accessing our secure server before you submit
sensitive information, check the document for your browser for
indication of an SSL connection (most browsers utilize an unbroken or
closed padlock). Verify that SSL is active before submitting sensitive
information to our server. To double-check, verify that the URL or
Address line of your browser for our site begins with "https."
It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to
your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished
using a shared computer.
Children
If you are under 18, you need parent/guardian permission to use a
credit card to make purchases online.
HOW TO CONTACT US
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you can contact
us at:
Girl Scouts–Arizona Cactus-Pine Council, Inc.
and we will get back to you as soon as possible.
Thank you for visiting our site.
This Privacy Policy was last updated in October 2014.
